(Sheldon:)Mommy, why are you crying?
'Cause I'm gonna
miss you, Shelly-bean,
(Sheldon:)even though you creep
the bugeeses out of me.
(Penny:)Okay, I guess
we're improvising now.
(Sheldon:)I'm sorry.
(Sheldon:)It's not my fault.
(Sheldon:)I'm just incredibly smart,
(Sheldon:)and everyone around here is
dumber than a bag of rocks.
(Sheldon:)Oh, now, don't
you start crying.
(Sheldon:)You get in that spaceship.
(Sheldon:)Mommy's late for
Indian bingo.
(Penny(on phone):)Mrs. Cooper, hey, it's Penny.
(Penny(on phone):)Yeah, I think I broke your son.
(Penny(on phone):)Hey, hold on.
(Penny(on phone):)Talk to your mother.
(Sheldon:)Mommy, I love you.
(Sheldon:)Don't let Spock take
me to the future!
(Bernadette:)Okay, Raj,
(Bernadette:)I know you've been avoiding me
and Howard, and I'm not leaving
(Bernadette:)until you tell me
what's going on
(Bernadette:)inside that little head
of yours.